Lee Hanni

Block 933A Hougang Avenue 9, #09-108, Singapore 531933 (65) 9176 5832 lavene88@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY AND OBJECTIVES

Responsible and meticulous Certified Practising Accountant, Australia with six years of experience in full set of accounts, variance analysis, budgeting and forecasting, as well as year-end audit and preparation of financial statements.

Seeking to use my past experience and technical skills to contribute towards the progress of the organization I work for and in return gain valuable work experience and achieve personal growth.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CapitaLand Mall Asia Limited

May 2011 - Present

Finance Executive, Apr 2014 to Present Senior Finance Assistant, Apr 2012 to Mar 2014 Finance Assistant, May 2011 to Mar 2012

- In charge of multiple full set of accounts (Current & previous portfolio includes mall, maintenance funds, management, marketing and investment holding companies.)
- Interact with different departments for monthly accruals, and accounting treatment clarification
- Trained and supervise 3 assistants in preparing accounting journals
- Improvise excel templates, increasing work efficiency
- Review of accounting journals, bank reconciliation, audit schedules, and GST return submission
- Monthly financial variance analysis upon closing of monthly accounts
- Cash flow management (Placement & withdrawal of funds)
- Preparation of Budget and Forecast, and Financial Statements/Annual report
- Assisted in system implementation centralized car park management system and budgeting system

CapitaLand Mall Asia Limited

Dec 2010 – Apr 2011

Finance Assistant (Temp; concurrent with university studies)

- Assisted in preparation of Financial Statements and Annual Reports
- Preparation of bank reconciliation and other administrative duties

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business (Accountancy)

RMIT University at Singapore Institute of Management, Singapore August 2011

Diploma in Chemical Process Technology (Food Technology)

Singapore Polytechnic, Singapore February 2008

LANGUAGE & SKILLS

Language English, Mandarin

Skills SAP ECC, XBRL BizFinx Filing system, Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint

CERTIFICATION

 Certified Practising Accountant, Australia September 2016

OTHERS

Current Salary: S\$3,620 (with 1 month AWS, 4 – 6 months VB)

Expected Salary: S\$4,300 (negotiable)

Earliest Commencement Date: One month notice period